Guide to the Mabou Mines Archive, 1966-2000 (bulk 1970-1995) MSS.133
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series X: Press, 145491
  - Subseries C: Productions, 145492
    - Company various publications Jan 1983, 145685 (Box 46, Folder 1841)
    - Company various publications Aug 1983 non-NY press, 145684 (Box 46, Folder 1842)
    - Company various publications Oct 1986 Iowa press, 145683 (Box 46, Folder 1843)
    - Company Austin American Statesman Sep 22, 24, 1987, 145682 (Box 46, Folder 1844)
    - Company Journal de Geneve Apr 17, 1991, 145681 (Box 46, Folder 1845)
    - Dead End Kids press package, 1980; 145680 (Box 46, Folder 1846)
    - Dead End Kids various publications Nov 1980, 145679 (Box 46, Folder 1847)
    - Dead End Kids various publications Dec 1980, 145678 (Box 46, Folder 1848)
    - Dead End Kids various publications Jan-May 1981, 145677 (Box 46, Folder 1849)
    - Dead End Kids various publications Amsterdam 1981, Hiroshima 1982, 1981-1982; 145676 (Box 46, Folder 1850)
    - Dead End Kids various publications Mar, May 1981 Toronto press, 145675 (Box 46, Folder 1851)
    - Dead End Kids various publications Feb-Mar 1982 includes Minneapolis, Seattle press, 145674 (Box 46, Folder 1852)
    - Dead End Kids Theater Summer/Fall 1982, 145673 (Box 46, Folder 1853)
    - Dead End Kids In Focus Jan 1983, 145672 (Box 46, Folder 1854)
    - Dead End Kids various publications Feb 1983 Philadelphia press, 145671 (Box 46, Folder 1855)
    - Dead End Kids various publications May 1983 Charleston, SC press, 145670 (Box 46, Folder 1856)
    - Dead End Kids Art Com Spring 1983, 145669 (Box 46, Folder 1857)
    - Dead End Kids various publications Feb 1984 Los Angeles press, 1983; 145668 (Box 46, Folder 1858)
    - Dead End Kids Olympic Arts Festival at Mark Taper Forum Jun 1-Aug 12 1984 festival program, 145667 (Box 46, Folder 1859)
    - Dead End Kids On Stage New York (Italian) Jul 1985, 145666 (Box 46, Folder 1860)
    - Dead End Kids (film) Village Voice, Rolling Stone Mar, Jun 1985, 145665 (Box 46, Folder 1861)
    - Dead End Kids (film) various publications Sep 1986 Toronto Film Festival, 145664 (Box 46, Folder 1862)
    - Dead End Kids (film) various publications Oct-Nov 1986, 145663 (Box 46, Folder 1863)
    - Dead End Kids (film) various publications Jan-Oct 1987, 145662 (Box 46, Folder 1864)
    - Dead End Kids advertisements Apr-May 1987 Apple Corps Theatre, 145661 (Box 46, Folder 1865)
    - Dead End Kids unidentified clippings, undated; 145660 (Box 46, Folder 1866)
    - Dressed Like an Egg various publications May 1977, 145659 (Box 46, Folder 1867)
    - Dressed Like an Egg NY Times, Wisdoms Child Sep-Oct 1977, 145658 (Box 46, Folder 1868)
    - Dressed Like an Egg various publications Mar, Aug/Sep 1978, 145657 (Box 46, Folder 1869)
    - Dressed Like an Egg various publications Mar 1980 Tasmanian and Australian press, 145656 (Box 46, Folder 1870)
    - Flow My Tears, The Policeman Said various publications May-Aug 1985 Boston press, 145655 (Box 46, Folder 1871)
    - Flow My Tears, The Policeman Said various publications Jun 1985-Jan 1986, 1985-1986; 145654 (Box 46, Folder 1872)
    - Flow My Tears, The Policeman Said various publications Feb-Jul 1988, 145653 (Box 46, Folder 1873)
    - Flow My Tears, The Policeman Said various publications miscellaneous/unidentified press, 1987-1990; 145652 (Box 46, Folder 1874)
    - Hajj various publications Jun-Oct 1982, 145651 (Box 46, Folder 1875)
    - Hajj various publications Jan-Oct 1983, 145650 (Box 46, Folder 1876)
    - Hajj various publications Apr, Jul, Aug 1984, 145649 (Box 46, Folder 1877)
    - Hajj various publications Aug 1984 Japan tour press, 145648 (Box 46, Folder 1878)
    - Hajj various publications Jun-Sep 1986, 145647 (Box 46, Folder 1879)
    - Hajj various publications Oct 1986 Minnesota press, 145646 (Box 46, Folder 1880)
    - Help Wanted various publications Feb 1986 NY reviews, 145645 (Box 46, Folder 1881)
    - Imagination Dead Imagine Village Voice Jun 26, 1984, 145644 (Box 46, Folder 1882)
    - Imagination Dead Imagine Industrial Design Sep/Oct 1984, 145643 (Box 46, Folder 1883)
    - Imagination Dead Imagine various publications May-Jul 1985, 145642 (Box 46, Folder 1884)
    - Imagination Dead Imagine EAR magazine Fall 1985, 145641 (Box 46, Folder 1885)
    - Imagination Dead Imagine various publications Apr 1986 MIT performance, 145640 (Box 46, Folder 1886)
    - Imagination Dead Imagine The Daily Iowan Oct 2, 1986, 145639 (Box 46, Folder 1887)
    - Imagination Dead Imagine various publications Apr 1987 Florida press, 145638 (Box 46, Folder 1888)
    - Imagination Dead Imagine New York News, undated; 145637 (Box 46, Folder 1889)
    - In the Jungle of Cities various publications Nov-Dec 1991, 145636 (Box 47, Folder 1890)
    - It's a Man's World various publications Aug-Sep 1985, 145635 (Box 47, Folder 1891)
    - It's a Man's World various publications Sep-Oct 1985, 145634 (Box 47, Folder 1892)
    - It's a Man's World various publications May 1987 Apple Corps Theatre, 145633 (Box 47, Folder 1893)
    - It's a Man's World various publications Jun 1987 Apple Corps Theatre, 145632 (Box 47, Folder 1894)
    - Lear various publications Sep-Dec 1987 Theatrical Outfit, Atlanta, 145631 (Box 47, Folder 1895)
    - Lear various publications Dec 1987-Jan 1988 New Jersey press, 1987-1988; 145630 (Box 47, Folder 1896)
    - Lear various publications Feb-Jun 1988, 145629 (Box 47, Folder 1897)
    - Lear various publications Jul-Aug 1988 Storm King press, 145628 (Box 47, Folder 1898)
    - Lear various publications Nov-Dec 1988, 145627 (Box 47, Folder 1899)
    - Lear West Side Spirit, Union News Jan, Mar 1989, 145626 (Box 47, Folder 1900)
    - Lear Theater Group Dec 1989, 145625 (Box 47, Folder 1901)
    - Lear various publications Jan 1990, 145624 (Box 47, Folder 1902)
    - Lear various publications Feb 1990, 145623 (Box 47, Folder 1903)
    - Lear various publications Mar 1990, 145622 (Box 47, Folder 1904)
    - Lear Dramatics Oct 1990, 145621 (Box 47, Folder 1905)
    - Lear The Sunday Star-Ledger Dec 30, 1990, 145620 (Box 47, Folder 1906)
    - Lear Théâtre/Public May-Jun 1991, 145619 (Box 47, Folder 1907)
    - Lear Toronto Star Mar 19, 1992, 145618 (Box 47, Folder 1908)
    - Lear Theatre Journal no. 45 "Mabou Mines's Lear: A Narrative of Collective Authorship" by Iris Smith, 1993; 145617 (Box 47, Folder 1909)
    - Lear various publications miscellaneous/unidentified press, undated; 145616 (Box 47, Folder 1910)
    - MahabharANTa various publications, 1992-1993; 145615 (Box 47, Folder 1911)
    - Mercier and Camier various publications, 1978-1979; 145614 (Box 47, Folder 1912)
    - The Mormon Project various publications, 1988-1990; 145613 (Box 47, Folder 1913)
    - Mother various publications, 1994-1995; 145612 (Box 47, Folder 1914)
    - Peter and Wendy Post and Courier (South Carolina) May 29, 1996, 145611 (Box 47, Folder 1914a)
    - A Prelude to Death in Venice various publications, 1979; 145610 (Box 47, Folder 1915)
    - A Prelude to Death in Venice New York Times May 1980 Frank Rich review, correspondence, 145609 (Box 47, Folder 1916)
    - A Prelude to Death in Venice various publications May-Aug 1980, 145608 (Box 47, Folder 1917)
    - A Prelude to Death in Venice various publications Aug-Oct 1980 San Francisco and Europe press, 145607 (Box 47, Folder 1918)
    - A Prelude to Death in Venice International Herald Tribune Oct 17, 1980, 145606 (Box 47, Folder 1919)
    - A Prelude to Death in Venice Scena Oct 1980, 145605 (Box 47, Folder 1920)
    - A Prelude to Death in Venice various publications Mar-Apr 1981, 145604 (Box 47, Folder 1921)
    - A Prelude to Death in Venice The Times (London), Financial Times Aug-Sep 1982, 145603 (Box 47, Folder 1922)
    - A Prelude to Death in Venice various publications Aug 1984 Japan press, 145602 (Box 47, Folder 1923)
    - A Prelude to Death in Venice various publications Mar, Aug 1985, 145601 (Box 47, Folder 1924)
    - A Prelude to Death in Venice / Hajj Village Voice May 1986, 145600 (Box 47, Folder 1925)
    - A Prelude to Death in Venice various publications May-Jun 1986, 145599 (Box 47, Folder 1926)
    - A Prelude to Death in Venice Village Voice Apr 14, 1987 advertisement, 145598 (Box 47, Folder 1927)
    - A Prelude to Death in Venice Twin Cities Reader Feb-Mar 1992, 145597 (Box 47, Folder 1928)
    - A Prelude to Death in Venice various publications miscellaneous/unidentified press, undated; 145596 (Box 47, Folder 1929)
    - Pretty Boy various publications Jun 1984, 145595 (Box 47, Folder 1930)
    - Pretty Boy various publications Jul 1984, 145594 (Box 47, Folder 1931)
    - Re-Cher-Chez various publications, 1980-1982; 145593 (Box 47, Folder 1932)
    - The Red Horse Animation New York Times Nov 20, 1970 [includes program], 145592 (Box 47, Folder 1933)
    - The Red Horse Animation various publications Oct-Nov 1971 Minneapolis, Seattle, Tacoma press, 145591 (Box 47, Folder 1934)
    - The Red Horse Animation Phoenix Dec 2, 1971, 145590 (Box 47, Folder 1935)
    - The Red Horse Animation various publications Nov 1971-Feb 1972 California press, 1971-1972; 145589 (Box 47, Folder 1936)
    - The Red Horse Animation various publications Jan-Feb 1972 Oregon press, 145588 (Box 47, Folder 1937)
    - The Red Horse Animation The Commercial Appeal (Memphis) Mar 11, 1972, 145587 (Box 47, Folder 1938)
    - Come and Go / The Red Horse Animation / The B. Beaver Animation New York Times Apr 22, 1972, 145586 (Box 47, Folder 1939)
    - The Red Horse Animation New York magazine May 15, 1972, 145585 (Box 47, Folder 1940)
    - The Red Horse Animation various publications Dec 1972 Netherlands press, 145584 (Box 47, Folder 1941)
    - The Red Horse Animation Financial Times (London) Jan 4, 1973, 145583 (Box 47, Folder 1942)
    - The Red Horse Animation / The B. Beaver Animation various publications NY performances, 1974; 145582 (Box 47, Folder 1943)
    - The Red Horse Animation New York Times Jul 30, 1974 re: Connecticut festival, 145581 (Box 47, Folder 1944)
    - The Red Horse Animation Soho Weely News May 1976, 145580 (Box 47, Folder 1945)
    - The Red Horse Animation Village Voice Nov 19, 1979 re: Animations playscript, 145579 (Box 47, Folder 1946)
    - The Red Horse Animation unidentified clipping, 1980; 145578 (Box 47, Folder 1947)
    - The Red Horse Animation DISSENT Fall 1987 "Individuals and Autonomists" by Ellen Levy, 145577 (Box 47, Folder 1948)
    - The Red Horse Animation San Francisco Examiner 1/12/?, undated; 152110 (Box 113, Folder 2372)
    - Reel to Real ASU West Thunder Press Dec 8, 1993 [includes ASU flyers], 145576 (Box 47, Folder 1949)
    - Reel to Real American Theatre Apr 1994, 145575 (Box 47, Folder 1950)
    - Reel to Real Village Voice, NY Times Apr 1994 advertisements, 145574 (Box 47, Folder 1951)
    - Reel to Real various publications Apr 1994, 145573 (Box 47, Folder 1952)
    - Reel to Real various publications Sep 1994 Duke University performance, 145572 (Box 47, Folder 1953)
    - Reel to Real American Theatre Nov 1994, 145571 (Box 47, Folder 1954)
    - The Saint and the Football Players various publications, 1973; 145570 (Box 47, Folder 1955)
    - The Saint and the Football Players Saturday Review Sep 20, 1975, 145569 (Box 47, Folder 1956)
    - The Saint and the Football Players various publications Feb 1976, 145568 (Box 47, Folder 1957)
    - The Saint and the Football Players The Villager Jul 22, 1976, 145567 (Box 47, Folder 1958)
    - The Saint and the Football Players various publications summer 1976 European press, 145566 (Box 47, Folder 1959)
    - The Shaggy Dog Animation Soho Weely News Dec 12, 1974, 145565 (Box 47, Folder 1960)
    - The Shaggy Dog Animation Village Voice Aug 2, 1976, 145564 (Box 47, Folder 1961)
    - The Shaggy Dog Animation various publications Jan-Apr 1978, 145563 (Box 47, Folder 1962)
    - The Shaggy Dog Animation various publications Feb-May 1978, 145562 (Box 47, Folder 1963)
    - The Shaggy Dog Animation Semiotext(e) Oct 20, 1978 proof, 145561 (Box 47, Folder 1964)
    - The Shaggy Dog Animation New Haven Advocate Apr 18, 1979, 145560 (Box 47, Folder 1965)
    - The Shaggy Dog Animation New Statesman Aug 1, 1980, 145559 (Box 47, Folder 1966)
    - The Shaggy Dog Animation various publications Dec 1985 Minnesota press, 145558 (Box 47, Folder 1967)
    - The Shaggy Dog Animation City Pages (Minneapolis) Oct 7, 1987, 145557 (Box 47, Folder 1968)
    - Sister Suzie Cinema various publications Jun-Jul 1980 reviews, 145556 (Box 47, Folder 1969)
    - Sister Suzie Cinema / A Prelude to Death in Venice various publications Aug-Sep 1980 Los Angeles press, 145555 (Box 47, Folder 1970)
    - Sister Suzie Cinema La Libre Belgique (Brussels) Sep 29, 1982, 145554 (Box 47, Folder 1971)
    - Sister Suzie Cinema The Yale Herald Apr 24, 1987, 145553 (Box 47, Folder 1972)
    - Sister Suzie Cinema (book) Theatre Times Jan 1988, 145552 (Box 47, Folder 1973)
    - Southern Exposure various publications Feb-Mar 1979 reviews, 145551 (Box 47, Folder 1974)
    - Southern Exposure various publications Feb-May 1979 listings, 145550 (Box 47, Folder 1975)
    - Southern Exposure various publications Jun-Oct 1979 reviews, 145549 (Box 47, Folder 1976)
    - Starcock various publications Dec 1985-Jan 1986 reviews, 1985-1986; 145548 (Box 47, Folder 1977)
    - Sueños La Jornada Aug 28, 1988, 145547 (Box 47, Folder 1978)
    - Sueños various publications Oct 1988 reviews, 145546 (Box 47, Folder 1979)
    - Sueños Art News Jan 1989, 145545 (Box 47, Folder 1980)
    - Sueños various publications Feb-Mar 1989 reviews, 145544 (Box 47, Folder 1981)
    - Sueños miscellaneous/unidentified press, 1985, 1986, undated; 145543 (Box 47, Folder 1982)
    - Through the Leaves various publications Feb-Apr 1984 reviews, 145542 (Box 47, Folder 1983)
    - Through the Leaves various publications May-Jun 1984 reviews, 145541 (Box 47, Folder 1984)
    - Through the Leaves [La Gazzetta?] Jul 10, 1984, 145540 (Box 47, Folder 1985)
    - Through the Leaves various publications Jul-Dec 1984, 145539 (Box 47, Folder 1986)
    - Through the Leaves various publications miscellaneous press with photocopy order forms, 1984; 145538 (Box 47, Folder 1987)
    - Through the Leaves various publications Apr-May 1985 Montreal press, 145537 (Box 47, Folder 1988)
    - Through the Leaves various publications Jun 1985-Jan 1986 Montreal press, 145536 (Box 47, Folder 1989)
    - Through the Leaves Washington Review Aug/Sep 1985, 145535 (Box 47, Folder 1990)
    - Through the Leaves unidentified publication Japanese press, unknown; 145534 (Box 47, Folder 1991)
    - Through the Leaves unidentified publication Israeli press, 1986; 145533 (Box 47, Folder 1992)
    - Through the Leaves (reconstruction) various publications Sep-Oct 1990, 145532 (Box 47, Folder 1993)
    - Vanishing Pictures various publications Feb-Mar 1980, Jan 1981, 1980-1981; 145531 (Box 47, Folder 1994)
    - Worstward Ho various publications Jun-Aug 1986, 145530 (Box 47, Folder 1995)
    - Worstward Ho various publications Sep 1986, 145529 (Box 47, Folder 1996)
    - Worstward Ho various publications Oct-Nov 1986, 145528 (Box 47, Folder 1997)
    - Worstward Ho various publications Apr 1991 Geneva press, 145527 (Box 47, Folder 1998)
    - Worstward Ho various publications Jan 1993 Kansas press, 145526 (Box 47, Folder 1999)
    - Wrong Guys various publications May 1981, 145525 (Box 47, Folder 2000)
    - Wrong Guys Zone magazine Fall/Winter 1981 feature, 145524 (Box 47, Folder 2001)
    - Wrong Guys PAJ vol. 6, no. 1 piece by Ruth Maleczech, 1981; 145523 (Box 47, Folder 2002)
    - The Gospel at Colonus production history, press quotes, awards, undated; 145522 (Box 48, Folder 2003)
    - The Gospel at Colonus various publications Jul 1982 Minneapolis press, 145521 (Box 48, Folder 2004)
    - The Gospel at Colonus various publications Aug-Sep 1982, 145520 (Box 48, Folder 2005)
    - The Gospel at Colonus various publications Aug-Sep 1982 UK press, 145519 (Box 48, Folder 2006)
    - The Gospel at Colonus New York Times Nov 11, 12, 1983 Pareles and Gussow reviews, 145518 (Box 48, Folder 2007)
    - The Gospel at Colonus various publications Nov-Dec 1983, 145517 (Box 48, Folder 2008)
    - The Gospel at Colonus various publications tour press, 1983-1984; 145516 (Box 48, Folder 2009)
    - The Gospel at Colonus various publications, 1984; 145515 (Box 48, Folder 2010)
    - The Gospel at Colonus Back Stage Jul 20, 1984, 145514 (Box 48, Folder 2011)
    - The Gospel at Colonus America's Arena, 1984-1985; 145513 (Box 48, Folder 2012)
    - The Gospel at Colonus various publications re: television broadcast, 1985; 145512 (Box 48, Folder 2013)
    - The Gospel at Colonus various publications tour press, 1985-1986; 145511 (Box 48, Folder 2014)
    - The Gospel at Colonus Arts Review vol. 3, no. 3, Spring 1986, 145510 (Box 48, Folder 2015)
    - The Gospel at Colonus various publications, 1987; 145509 (Box 48, Folder 2016)
    - The Gospel at Colonus ELLE Feb 1988, 145508 (Box 48, Folder 2017)
    - The Gospel at Colonus various publications Mar 1988 re: Broadway premiere, 145507 (Box 48, Folder 2018)
    - The Gospel at Colonus various publications Apr 1988 re: Broadway, 145506 (Box 48, Folder 2019)
    - The Gospel at Colonus various publications May 1988 re: Broadway, 145505 (Box 48, Folder 2020)
    - The Gospel at Colonus May 16, 1988 Breuer's letter declining Tony nomination, 145504 (Box 48, Folder 2021)
    - The Gospel at Colonus plays INTERNATIONAL Jun-Jul 1988, 145503 (Box 48, Folder 2022)
      - Villager Downtown Theater Awards, 1982; 145832 (Box 45, Folder 1696)
    - The Gospel at Colonus Village Voice Jul 17, 1990, 145502 (Box 48, Folder 2023)
    - The Gospel at Colonus various publications Oct 1990 California press, 145501 (Box 48, Folder 2024)
    - The Gospel at Colonus OC Weekly Feb 28-Mar 6, 1997, 145500 (Box 48, Folder 2025)
    - Lulu various publications, 1981; 145499 (Box 48, Folder 2026)
    - Prisoner of Love various publications Jun 1995, 145498 (Box 48, Folder 2027)
    - Warrior Ant Village Voice Jun 4, 1985, 145497 (Box 48, Folder 2028)
    - Warrior Ant Theater Spring 1987 also: Akalaitis's "Green Card", 145496 (Box 48, Folder 2029)
    - Warrior Ant Village Voice Aug 30, 1988, 145495 (Box 48, Folder 2030)
    - Warrior Ant various publications Oct-Nov 1988, 145494 (Box 48, Folder 2031)
    - Warrior Ant American Theatre Jun 1991, 145493 (Box 48, Folder 2032)
- Series XI: Objects, 145835
  Objects and props from Mabou Mines productions. Of particular interest are the puppets Rose [ Shaggy Dog Animation] and John [ Prelude to Death in Venice], and the shadow puppets from the MahabharANTa.
  - Geiger counter Dead End Kids, undated; 145888 (Box 163, Folder 133.2.0001)
  - Steinite tube radio/amplifier Dead End Kids, undated; 145887 (Object 133.2.0002)
  - Glass x-ray slides Dead End Kids, undated; 145886 (Box 163, Folder 133.2.0003)
  - Hand mirrors Dressed Like an Egg, undated; 145885 (Box 163, Folder 133.2.0004)
  - Light shoes Dressed Like an Egg, undated; 145884 (Box 163, Folder 133.2.0005)
  - Painting of woman at mirror Dressed Like an Egg, undated; 145883 (Object 133.2.0006)
  - Celastic dress by Ree Morton Dressed Like an Egg, Undated; 133.2.0007; 145882; 1 item one dress (Object 133.2.0007)
    Dress is large and difficult to move. Access is contingent on curatorial approval.
    Artist: Ree Morton
    Props (object genres)
  - Celastic scarf by Ree Morton Dressed Like an Egg, Undated; 133.2.0008; 145881; 1 item one scarf (Object 133.2.0008)
  - Celastic scarf by Ree Morton Dressed Like an Egg, Undated; 133.2.0009; 145880; 1 item one scarf (Object 133.2.0009)
  - Comedy mask The Mormon Project, undated; 145879 (Box not specified, Folder 133.2.0010)
  - Comedy mask The Mormon Project, undated; 145878 (Box not specified, Folder 133.2.0011)
  - Comedy mask The Mormon Project, undated; 145877 (Box not specified, Folder 133.2.0012)
  - Comedy mask The Mormon Project, undated; 145876 (Box not specified, Folder 133.2.0013)
  - Tragedy mask The Mormon Project, undated; 145875 (Box not specified, Folder 133.2.0014)
  - Tragedy mask The Mormon Project, undated; 145874 (Box not specified, Folder 133.2.0015)
  - Tragedy mask The Mormon Project, undated; 145873 (Box not specified, Folder 133.2.0016)
  - Red Horse mounts The Red Horse Animation, undated; 145872 (Box 159)
  - Sueños designs Sueños, 1988; 145871 (Box 159)
  - Sueños model pieces Sueños, undated; 145870 (Box 162, Folder 133.2.0019)
  - Painted celastic swaths Dressed Like an Egg [?], Undated; 133.2.0020; 145869; 2 items two pieces of painted celastic fabric (Object 133.2.0020)
  - Rose The Shaggy Dog Animation, undated; 145868 (Object 133.2.0021)
    Scope and Content note
    Dummy with extra clothing in case.
  - John A Prelude to Death in Venice, undated (Object 133.2.0022)
  - Airplane shadow puppet, undated; 145866 (Box 160, Folder 133.2.0023)
  - Building shadow puppet, undated; 145865 (Box 160, Folder 133.2.0024)
  - Tank shadow puppet, undated; 145864 (Box 160, Folder 133.2.0025)
  - Arrows MahabharANTa shadow puppet, undated; 145863 (Box 160, Folder 133.2.0026)
  - Spider MahabharANTa shadow puppet, undated; 145862 (Box 160, Folder 133.2.0027)
  - Spider shadow puppet, undated; 145861 (Box 160, Folder 133.2.0028)
  - Antjuna MahabharANTa shadow puppet, undated; 145860 (Box 160, Folder 133.2.0029)
  - Chariot MahabharANTa shadow puppet, undated; 145859 (Box 160, Folder 133.2.0030)
  - Traditional female dancers MahabharANTa shadow puppet, undated; 145858 (Box 160, Folder 133.2.0031)
  - Bowmen MahabharANTa shadow puppet, undated; 145857 (Box 160, Folder 133.2.0032)
  - Antjuna with bow MahabharANTa shadow puppet, undated; 145856 (Box 160, Folder 133.2.0033)
  - Gundul and Wajil MahabharANTa shadow puppet, undated; 145855 (Box 160, Folder 133.2.0034)
  - Dragonfly MahabharANTa shadow puppet, undated; 145854 (Box 161, Folder 133.2.0035)
  - Small female insect MahabharANTa shadow puppet, undated; 145853 (Box 161, Folder 133.2.0036)
  - Crest MahabharANTa shadow puppet, undated; 145852 (Box 161, Folder 133.2.0037)
  - Insect wings MahabharANTa shadow puppet, undated; 145851 (Box 161, Folder 133.2.0038)
  - Flower MahabharANTa shadow puppet, undated; 145850 (Box 161, Folder 133.2.0039)
  - Sword MahabharANTa shadow puppet, undated; 145849 (Box 161, Folder 133.2.0040)
  - Wrenches MahabharANTa shadow puppet, undated; 145848 (Box 161, Folder 133.2.0041)
  - Arrow MahabharANTa shadow puppet, undated; 145847 (Box 161, Folder 133.2.0042)
  - Telephone MahabharANTa shadow puppet, undated; 145846 (Box 161, Folder 133.2.0043)
  - Female reptiles MahabharANTa shadow puppet, undated; 145845 (Box 161, Folder 133.2.0044)
  - Ape MahabharANTa shadow puppet, undated; 145844 (Box 161, Folder 133.2.0045)
  - Rat MahabharANTa shadow puppet, undated; 145843 (Box 161, Folder 133.2.0046)
  - Boar MahabharANTa shadow puppet, undated; 145842 (Box 161, Folder 133.2.0047)
  - Alligator MahabharANTa shadow puppet, undated; 145841 (Box 161, Folder 133.2.0048)
  - Camel MahabharANTa shadow puppet, undated; 145840 (Box 161, Folder 133.2.0049)
  - Reptile MahabharANTa shadow puppet, undated; 145839 (Box 161, Folder 133.2.0050)
  - Frog MahabharANTa shadow puppet, undated; 145838 (Box 161, Folder 133.2.0051)
  - Hippo MahabharANTa shadow puppet, undated; 145837 (Box 161, Folder 133.2.0052)
  - extra wooden rod shadow puppet, undated; 145836 (Box 161, Folder 133.2.0053)
  - "Pest Chaser: ultrasonic repellent" [w/ Dead End Kids production files], undated; 152149 (Box not specified, Folder 133.2.0054)
- Series XII: Financial Files, Grants, and Development, 145320